Guide to the Office of the President records, 1795-2007 RG0002
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Lloyd H. Elliott records, 1927-1989; 1965-1988; Series 4; 62.5 Linear Feet 39 record center cartons, 8 document boxes
  - University oganization files, 1953-1974; 1958-1972; Series 4 Sub-series 4; 13.5 Linear Feet 9 record center cartons
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: General, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: General, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: General, 1969-1970 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: Black Students Union, 1968-1972 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: Dean of Men, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: Dean of Students, 1966-1967 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: Housing, 1971-1972 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: Liberal Education/Action Project - LEAP, 1964-1965 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: Internation Students, 1965-1969 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: (Foreign Students, Advisory to), 1964 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: Marvin Center, 1968-1970 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: Marvin Center Boards, 1969-1972 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: Resolutions, Rules & Regulations "Students", 1968-1972 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for: Statement of Student Rights & Responsibilities (History of), 1968-1970 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Student Activities: General (See Student Affairs, Vice President - General), 1967-1972 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Student Activities: General, 1958-1962 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Student Activities: Hatchet (See Student Publications Committee for other papers), 1964 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Student Activities: Student Assembly, 1969-1970 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Student Activities: Student Committee - Student Board of Trustees, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Student Activities: Student Council, 1966-1968 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Student Activities: Student Council, 1964-1965 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Student Activities: Students for a Democratic Society (Not in Box), undated (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Student Protests & Demonstrations: General, 04/1971-05/1971 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Student Protests & Demonstrations: General, 1968-1969 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Student Protests & Demonstrations: Correspondence re, 1968-1969 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Student Protests & Demonstrations: General, 1967-1968 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Student Protests & Demonstrations: General, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Student Protests & Demonstrations: Hershey Question, 1967-1968 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Student Protests & Demonstrations: Hershey Decision, Letters re, 1967-1968 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Student Protests & Demonstrations: Maury Hall Incident (Sino-Soviet Institute), 1969 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Student Protests & Demonstrations: Student Strike, 05/1970 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Student Protests & Demonstrations: War Moratorium, 11/1969 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Student Protests & Demonstrations: Watergate Demonstration, 02/19/1970 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Student Services: Director of Student Health (Not in Box), undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Student Services: Testing & Counselling Center, 1958-1965 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Student Services: Director of Travel (Discontinued 1967), 1966-1967 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Student Services: Director of Veterans Education, 1966-1967 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Student Affairs: Troubadours, 1959-1961 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Student Affairs: Workshop for Careers in the Arts, 1968-1972 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: General, 1968-1971 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: General, 1960-1968 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Benefits - Faculty - Staff, 1966-1967 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Business Office, 1960-1972 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Comptroller, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Education Opportunity Programs (EOP), Inner City Grants (Not in Box), 1970-1973 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: EOP, Inner City Grants (Not in Box), 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Faulty Salaries, 1963-1967 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Perkins & Will - Master Plan of the University, 1964-1965 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Personnel Office, 1965-1968 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Property, 1960-1972 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Property, 1957-1959 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Samson, Henry W. (Estate of), undated (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Scholarships, 1964-1965 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Scholarships, 1960-1965 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Scholarships - Marshall, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Scholarships - Newspaper, 1962-1964 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Scholarships - Rhodes, 1962-1964 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Student Financial Aid, 1961-1972 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Treasurer and Vice President: Tuition and Student Fees, 1961-1971 (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Organizational files, 1968-1988; 1973-1977; Series 4 Sub-series 5; 10.5 Linear Feet 7 record center cartons
    This set of organizational files was received from the office of the president in 1999. Formerly accession #768.
    This sub-series is a set of organizational files, which are files of correspondence and other materials organized by the university unit to which they relate. University organizational files are differentiated from the alphabetical correspondence files in that they pertain exclusively to correspondents and subjects internal to the university.
    This set of files appears to have been used most heavily around the period 1973-1977, although they include documents both before and after that period.
    Subjects include the sesquicentennial, University historian, Reagan assassination attempt, University Marshal, sponsored research, regulations regarding student organizations, ceremonies and convocations, building dedications, standing committees, burial grounds owned by GW, and experimental programs.
    - All University Assembly: President Elliott's Report on All University Assembly Report for all University Senate, 08/14/1974 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - All University Assembly: All University Steering Committee-General, 1971-1974 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - All University Assembly: All University Assembly Proposal for All University Senate, 10/1973 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1970-1984 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - President's Office: International Programs - General, 1974-1975 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - President's Office: International Programs - Iran - General, 1974-1975 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Athletics (General), 1975-1979 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Budget Director: Budget, undated (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Budget Director: Director of Planning & Budgeting (General), 1975-1979 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Marshal: Medical School Commencement, 05/26/1978 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Marshal: Commencement, Medicine, 05/27/1977 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Marshal: Commencement, 05/08/1977 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Marshal: Commencement-Law Center, 05/22/1977 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Marshal: Convocation, 02/1977 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Marshal: Commencment-National Law Center, 05/1976 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Marshal: Commencement-School of Medicine, 05/1976 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Marshal: Commencement, 05/1976 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Marshal: Commencement-Law, 05/25/1975 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Marshal: Commencement-Medicine, 05/23/1975 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Marshal: Convocation, 02/1976 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Marshal: Commencement, 05/1975 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Marshal: Convocation, 02/17/1975 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Marshal: The Shah of Iran-Honorary Degree, (Special Convocation-Mohammad Reza Shah Pahlevi), 06/05/1974 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Marshal: Commencement, 05/05/1974 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Marshal: Commencements, Law & Medicine, 05/26/1974 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Marshal: Convocation, 02/18/1974 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Marshal: Commencement, Medicine & Law, 05/27/1973-06/03/1973 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Marshal: Commencement, Elliott Richardson, Speaker) Columbian College-Cancelled, 05/1973-06/1973 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Marshal: Convocation, 02/19/1973 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Marshal: Commencement, 05/1973 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Academic Affairs, Vice President-General, 1973-1978 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Academic Editor, 1964-1975 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Admissions Office, General, 1973-1975 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Art Curator-General, 1973-1977 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Columbian College of Arts and Sciences: General, 1973-1979 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Columbian College of Arts and Sciences: Art Department, Corcoran Gallery Affiliation, 1941-1972 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Columbian College of Arts and Sciences: Departments, Columbian College, 1972-1979 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Education, School of: General, 1973-1975 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Education, School of: ERIC, 1973-1975 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Education, School of: National Council on Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Engineering & Applied Science, School of-General, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Engineering & Applied Science-Solar Energy Research Insitute, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Experimental Programs, Division of (Academic Affairs-General), 1974-1975 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Experimental Programs, Div. of (Acad. Affairs-General), 1973 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - General Studies, College of (General), 1973 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - General Studies, College of (General), 1974-1975 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - General Studies, College of: Air University (CGS), 1962-1987 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - General Studies, College of: Army War College (CGS), 1963-1969 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - General Studies, College of Army War College Carlisle Barracks, PA, 1960-1961 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - General Studies, College of National War College, Ft. McNair, 1961-1963 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - General Studies, College of: National War College (Public & International Affairs), undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - General Studies, College of: Naval War College (Public & International Affairs), undated (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - General Studies, College of: College of General Studies-Newport Visit, undated (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - General Studies, College of: College of General Studies-Acting Dean Galbreath, Asst. R.B. Simons, undated (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - General Studies, College of: Industrial College of the Armed Forces (CGS), undated (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - General Studies, College of: General Studies-Industrial College of the Armed Forces, 1960-1963 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Government and Bus. Administration: General, 1973-1975 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Government and Business Administration: Business Advisory Board, undated (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Government and Business Administration: School of Government & Business Administration Fellowship Programs, undated (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: General, 1973-1975 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Consortium Committee-Burns Report, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Consortium-General, 07/1975-12/1975 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Consortium-General, 01/1975-06/1974 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Consortium-Tenth Anniversary Dinner, 01/17/1974 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Consortium Material-LHE, 10/1973 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Consortium General, 07/1973-12/1973 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Consortium Proposal-Educational Opportunity Program, undated (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Consortium of Universities-Proposal for AED, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Consortium-Articles of Incorporation & Bylaws, undated (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Consortium-Student Financial Aid, undated (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Consortium-Task Force, undated (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences Fellowship, undated (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Graduate School Forensic Sciences-Dept. of, undated (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Forensic Sciences Dept. Proposal Background, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 30)
    - Law Center: General, 1973-1975 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Law Center: National Law Center, HEW On-Site Visit, 01/1975-03/1975 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Libraries: General, 1973-1975 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Libraries: Academic Affairs-Librarian, University, undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Libraries: Library Dedication Public & International Affairs, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Sino-Soviet Studies Institute (Public & International Affairs), undated (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Registrar's Office-General, 1973-1975 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Summer Sessions-General, 1973-1975 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Summer Sessions-General, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Vice President for Administration-General, undated (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Vice Presidnet for Administration: US vs Butler Case Correspondence, undated (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Vice Presidnet for Administration for Personnel Services, 1973-1975 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Vice Presidnet for Administration for Campus Security, 1973-1975 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Vice Presidnet for Administration for Campus Security (U.S. vs Butler Rape Case), undated (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Sponsored Research-General, 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Sponsored Research-Agency for International Development (AID), 1975 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Vice President for Development, 1973-1975 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Vice President for Development: Alumni Office-General Info., 1973-1975 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Vice President for Development: Annual Support Program, 1973-1975 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Vice President for Development: Public Relations, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP (General), 1975 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Med. Center (General), 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Med. Center (General), 1973 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Med. Center-Epidemiology & Environmental Health, Dept. of, 1973-1975 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Medical Center- Hospital (General), 1973-1975 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Medical Center-Medical Center Problems (Background Papers-Dr. Elliott #2), 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Medical Center-Medical Center Problems,(Dr. Elliott, Background Papers #1), undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affirs, VP-Medical Center Problems, Clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Medical Center, Medicine, Chair of Dept.-Jensen/Feffer, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Medical Center-Medicine, Chair of Dept.-Jensen/Feffer, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Medical Center-President's Task Force for Medical Center, 1971-1972 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Medicine, School of-General, 1972-1975 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Medical Center, Medicine & Health Sciences, School of-Dedication, 05/24/1973 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Medical Center, Med. School Faculty Ordinances, undated (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP for Medical Center-School of Medicine, Tuition Budget, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Medical Center, Legislation, GWU-GU, Med.-Dent, 1976-1981 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Medical Center, Legislation, GWU-GU, Med.-Dent, 1973-1975 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Medical Center: Medical Affairs, VP-Medical Center-Legislation, GWU-GU, Med.-Dent, Testimony, Mazzoli Subcommittee, 01/24/1974 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Medical Center: Ordinances for Faculty and Staff of Medical School, undated (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects-VP for, 1973-1975 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Policy Studies Health Staff Seminar, 1971-1975 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects, Washington Institute for Educational Leadership (Ford Foundation), 1974 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects, Washington Institute for Educational Leadership (Ford Foundation), 1973 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President-General, 1973-1975 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President: Human Relations Act-Non-discrimination, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Student Affairs, VP-Housing, 1973-1975 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Student Affairs, Marvin Center-General, 1973-1975 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Student Affairs, VP-Marvin Center Boards, 1973-1975 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Student Activities-General, 1973-1975 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Student Activities-Hatchet, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Student Affairs, VP-Student Government, 1973-1975 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Student Rights & Responsibilities (Student Affairs), 1967-1971 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President: Approval of Regulations Governing Student Organizations-Board of Trustees, Incl. Rule 6, 1928-1958 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Treasurer, Vice President and-Educational Opportunity Programs Inner City Grants, 1970-1973 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Treasurer, VP-Educational Opportunity, undated (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Treasurer & Vice President: Programs Inner City Grants, 1968-1969 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Treasurer, VP, 1973-1976 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Treasurer & Vice President: Business Office, 1973-1975 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Treasurer & Vice President: Property, 1973-1977 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Treasurer & Vice President: Treasurer's Office, Student Financial Aid, 1973-1978 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Senate, University: Academic Forum, 1969-1974 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Senate, University: General, 1973-1975 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Senate, University: Lists, 1973-1975 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Senate, University: Resolutions, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Senate, University: Meeting, US vs. Butler Case, 02/09/1973 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Senate, University: Executive Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Senate, University: Executive Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Senate, University: Special Committee, School of Medicine Problems, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Senate, University: Public Ceremonies Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Senate, University: Public Ceremonies (Senate), 1971-1973 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Organizational files, 1970-1987; 1976-1985; Series 4 Sub-series 6; 4.5 Linear Feet 3 record center cartons
    This set of organizational files was received from the office of the president in 1992. Formerly accession #165.
    This sub-series is a set of "organization" files, which are files of correspondence and other materials organized by the university unit to which they relate. University organization files are differentiated from the alphabetical correspondence files in that they pertain exclusively to correspondents and subjects internal to the university.
    The bulk of these files date from around 1976 to 1985, although they contain material from both before and after that period.
    - Advisory Committees and Councils: Departmental & Student memberships, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Advisory Committees and Councils: Councils - Membership Lists (President's Office), undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Advisory Committees and Councils: Advisory Committees - Departmental, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Advisory Committees and Councils: Councils - General Information, undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Advisory Committees and Councils: Faculty Assembly - General, undated (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - International Programs, Special Assistant for (Grub):, undated (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - International Programs, Special Assistant for (Grub): International Programs - Iran, undated (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - International Programs, Special Assistant for (Grub): Iran (publicity), undated (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - International Programs, Special Assistant for (Grub): Iran (agreement, etc.), undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - International Programs, Special Assistant for (Grub): General, undated (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Marshall: Opening Convocation, 09/21/1985 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Marshall: Commencement, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Marshall: Special Convocation: (Mircéa Eliade), 1985 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Marshall: Honors Convocation, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Marshall: Commencement, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Marshall: Convocation, 02/17/1985 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Marshall: Opening Convocation, 09/1984 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Marshall: Commencement, 1983 (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Marshall: Convocation, 02/21/1983 (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Marshall: Opening Convocation, 09/1983 (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - Marshall: Opening Convocation, 09/1982 (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - Marshall: Commencement, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Marshall: Convocation, 02/15/1982 (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Marshall: Opening Convocation, 09/1981 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Marshall: Graduation, 05/1981 (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - Marshall: Convocation, 02/16/1981 (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Marshall: Graduation, 05/1980 (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - Marshall: Convocation, 02/18/1980 (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Provost's Office:, undated (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - Assistant Provost for Affirmative Action, undated (Box 77, Folder 31)
    - Athletics - General, undated (Box 77, Folder 32)
    - Athletics - Smith Center, undated (Box 77, Folder 33)
    - Athletics - NCAA, undated (Box 77, Folder 34)
    - Comptroller's Office (empty folder), undated (Box 77, Folder 35)
    - Director of Planning & Budgeting - General, undated (Box 77, Folder 36)
    - Compute Center:, undated (Box 77, Folder 37)
    - Computer Center - General, undated (Box 77, Folder 38)
    - Academic Affairs:, undated (Box 77, Folder 39)
    - Academic Affairs, Vice President for (General ), undated (Box 77, Folder 40)
    - Admissions Office General, undated (Box 77, Folder 41)
    - Admissions: Admissions Policy on Integration (Admissions Office), undated (Box 77, Folder 42)
    - Admissions: Readmission of Students (Admissions Office), undated (Box 77, Folder 43)
    - Art Curator - General, undated (Box 77, Folder 44)
    - Continuing Education & Summer Sessions: General, undated (Box 77, Folder 45)
    - Continuing Education & Summer Sessions: Accreditation (CE&SS), undated (Box 77, Folder 46)
    - Continuing Education & Summer Sessions: Degree Changes - General, undated (Box 77, Folder 47)